<resources>
    <string name="app_name">GreenGenie</string>
    <string name="txt_tab1">My Genie</string>
    <string name="txt_tab2">My Data</string>
    <string name="txt_tab3">Form</string>
    <string name="lamp">My Genie</string>
    <string name="user">Profile</string>
    <string name="data">Data</string>
    <string name="form">Form</string>
    <string name="save">Save</string>

    <string name="water_sentc">Introduce the amount of your last water bill</string>
    <string name="water_sentc2">Introduce the price of your last water bill</string>
    <string name="light_sentc">Introduce the amount of your last light bill</string>
    <string name="light_sentc2">Introduce the price of your last light bill</string>
    <string name="gas_sentc">Introduce the amount of your last gas bill</string>
    <string name="gas_sentc2">Introduce the price of your last gas bill</string>
    <string name="petrol_sentc">Introduce the amount of your last petrol bill</string>
    <string name="petrol_sentc2">Introduce the price of your last petrol bill</string>
    <string name="people_sentc">How many people lives in your house?</string>
    <string name="house_sentc">Introduce the surface of your house</string>

    <string name="btnDone">Done</string>
    <string name="btnCancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="btnFix">Fix Objective</string>
    <string name="btnDelete">Delete</string>
    <string name="btnEdit">Edit</string>
    <string name="btnNewForm">New Form</string>
    <string name="spinnerBill">Select month</string>
    <string name="LogOut">Log Out</string>
    <string name="editProfile">Edit Profile</string>
    <string name="nameProfile">Profile Name</string>
    <string name="emailProfile">Profile email</string>
    <string name="spinner">Vehicle Type</string>


    <string name="text_policy">POLÍTICA DE PRIVACIDAD \n\n

    El presente Política de Privacidad establece los términos en que GreenGenie usa y protege la información que es proporcionada por sus usuarios al momento de utilizar su sitio web. Esta compañía está comprometida con la seguridad de los datos de sus usuarios. Cuando le pedimos llenar los campos de información personal con la cual usted pueda ser identificado, lo hacemos asegurando que sólo se empleará de acuerdo con los términos de este documento. Sin embargo esta Política de Privacidad puede cambiar con el tiempo o ser actualizada por lo que le recomendamos y enfatizamos revisar continuamente esta página para asegurarse que está de acuerdo con dichos cambios.\n\n

    Información que es recogida \n\n

    Nuestro sitio web podrá recoger información personal por ejemplo: Nombre,  información de contacto como  su dirección de correo electrónica e información demográfica. Así mismo cuando sea necesario podrá ser requerida información específica para procesar algún pedido o realizar una entrega o facturación.\n\n

    Uso de la información recogida \n\n

    Nuestro sitio web emplea la información con el fin de proporcionar el mejor servicio posible, particularmente para mantener un registro de usuarios, de pedidos en caso que aplique, y mejorar nuestros productos y servicios.  Es posible que sean enviados correos electrónicos periódicamente a través de nuestro sitio con ofertas especiales, nuevos productos y otra información publicitaria que consideremos relevante para usted o que pueda brindarle algún beneficio, estos correos electrónicos serán enviados a la dirección que usted proporcione y podrán ser cancelados en cualquier momento. \n\n

    GreenGenie está altamente comprometido para cumplir con el compromiso de mantener su información segura. Usamos los sistemas más avanzados y los actualizamos constantemente para asegurarnos que no exista ningún acceso no autorizado. \n\n

    Cookies \n\n

    Una cookie se refiere a un fichero que es enviado con la finalidad de solicitar permiso para almacenarse en su ordenador, al aceptar dicho fichero se crea y la cookie sirve entonces para tener información respecto al tráfico web, y también facilita las futuras visitas a una web recurrente. Otra función que tienen las cookies es que con ellas las web pueden reconocerte individualmente y por tanto brindarte el mejor servicio personalizado de su web. \n\n

    Nuestro sitio web emplea las cookies para poder identificar las páginas que son visitadas y su frecuencia. Esta información es empleada únicamente para análisis estadístico y después la información se elimina de forma permanente. Usted puede eliminar las cookies en cualquier momento desde su ordenador. Sin embargo las cookies ayudan a proporcionar un mejor servicio de los sitios web, estás no dan acceso a información de su ordenador ni de usted, a menos de que usted así lo quiera y la proporcione directamente noticias. Usted puede aceptar o negar el uso de cookies, sin embargo la mayoría de navegadores aceptan cookies automáticamente pues sirve para tener un mejor servicio web. También usted puede cambiar la configuración de su ordenador para declinar las cookies. Si se declinan es posible que no pueda utilizar algunos de nuestros servicios. \n\n

    Enlaces a Terceros \n\n

    Este sitio web pudiera contener enlaces a otros sitios que pudieran ser de su interés. Una vez que usted de clic en estos enlaces y abandone nuestra página, ya no tenemos control sobre al sitio al que es redirigido y por lo tanto no somos responsables de los términos o privacidad ni de la protección de sus datos en esos otros sitios terceros. Dichos sitios están sujetos a sus propias políticas de privacidad por lo cual es recomendable que los consulte para confirmar que usted está de acuerdo con estas. \n\n

    Control de su información personal \n\n

    En cualquier momento usted puede restringir la recopilación o el uso de la información personal que es proporcionada a nuestro sitio web.  Cada vez que se le solicite rellenar un formulario, como el de alta de usuario, puede marcar o desmarcar la opción de recibir información por correo electrónico.  En caso de que haya marcado la opción de recibir nuestro boletín o publicidad usted puede cancelarla en cualquier momento. \n\n

    Esta compañía no venderá, cederá ni distribuirá la información personal que es recopilada sin su consentimiento, salvo que sea requerido por un juez con una orden judicial. \n\n

    GreenGenie Se reserva el derecho de cambiar los términos de la presente Política de Privacidad en cualquier momento. \n\n

    Esta politica de privacidad se han generado en politicadeprivacidadplantilla.com.</string>

    <string name ="Policy_eng">PRIVACY POLICY \n\n

The present Privacy Policy sets the terms in which GreenGenie uses and protects the information provided by its users when using its website. This company is committed to the security of its users\' data. When we ask you to fill in personal information fields that can identify you, we do so by ensuring that it will only be used in accordance with the terms of this document. However, this Privacy Policy may change over time or be updated, so we recommend and emphasize that you continuously check this page to ensure that you agree with such changes.\n\n

Information Collected\n\n

Our website may collect personal information such as Name, contact information such as your email address and demographic information. Similarly, specific information may be required to process an order or to make a delivery or billing when necessary.\n\n

Use of Collected Information\n\n

Our website uses the information to provide the best possible service, particularly to keep a record of users, orders if applicable, and improve our products and services. Periodic emails may be sent through our site with special offers, new products and other advertising information that we consider relevant to you or that can provide some benefit, these emails will be sent to the address you provide and can be canceled at any time.\n\n

GreenGenie is highly committed to complying with the commitment to keep your information safe. We use the most advanced systems and constantly update them to ensure that there is no unauthorized access.\n\n

Cookies\n\n

A cookie refers to a file that is sent with the purpose of requesting permission to be stored on your computer. Upon accepting such file, a cookie is created and it serves to keep information about web traffic and also facilitates future visits to a recurring website. Another function of cookies is that they allow the website to recognize you individually and therefore provide you with the best personalized service from its website.\n\n

Our website uses cookies to identify pages that are visited and their frequency. This information is only used for statistical analysis and the information is then permanently deleted. You can delete cookies at any time from your computer. However, cookies help to provide a better service from websites, they do not give access to information from your computer or you, unless you want it and provide it directly. You can accept or reject the use of cookies, however most browsers accept cookies automatically as it serves to have a better web service. You can also change the settings on your computer to decline cookies. If they are declined, it is possible that you will not be able to use some of our services.\n\n

Third-party links\n\n

This website may contain links to other sites that may be of interest to you. Once you click on these links and leave our page, we no longer have control over the information you provide to these third-party sites. Therefore, we are not responsible for the protection and privacy of any information that you provide while visiting such sites. These third-party sites have their own privacy policies, so it is advisable to consult them before providing any personal information.\n\n

Controlling your personal information\n\n

You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information by contacting us at the address provided below.\n\n

GreenGenie Security\n\n

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. \n\n
    Control of Your Personal Information\n\n

At any time, you can restrict the collection or use of personal information provided to our website. Whenever you are asked to fill out a form, such as a user registration form, you can choose to receive or not to receive information by email. If you have chosen to receive our newsletter or advertising, you can cancel it at any time.\n\n

This company will not sell, transfer, or distribute personal information that is collected without your consent, unless required by a court order.\n\n

GreenGenie reserves the right to change the terms of this Privacy Policy at any time.\n\n

This privacy policy was generated on politicadeprivacidadplantilla.com.</string>


    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="genie_tips">HI!!! I´m GreenGenie!! \n\n
        I´m going to be your assistant to help you saving money, and... being ecofriendly!!</string>
    <string name="title_activity_forgot_password">ForgotPassword</string>
    <!-- Strings used for fragments for navigation -->
    <string name="first_fragment_label">First Fragment</string>
    <string name="second_fragment_label">Second Fragment</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="previous">Previous</string>

    <string name="hello_first_fragment">Hello first fragment</string>
    <string name="hello_second_fragment">Hello second fragment. Arg: %1$s</string>
    <string name="createform">Form created</string>
    <string name="formerror">Error creating form</string>

</resources>

